{"id":"2018_11","name":"","memoryVerse":"\"The Lord does not look at the things people look at. People look at the outward appearance, but the Lord looks at the heart.\" â€“ 1 Samuel 16:7b","dayQuestions":{"one":{"title":"FIRST DAY: Read the notes and the references.","questions":[{"id":"2018_11_1","questionText":"1. Use this space to record how you have seen God's activity during the week. (How has He provided, answered, comforted, reconciled, guided, etc.?)","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_11_2","questionText":"2. From the past week's study, what made the most significant impact to you in the notes, lecture, group sharing or personal study?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"two":{"title":"SECOND DAY: Read Psalm 139.\nPsalms compile song lyrics and prayers from many authors. This lesson focuses on the Psalms David wrote.","readVerse":[{"book":"Psalm","verse":"139:1-999"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_11_3","questionText":"3. What do you learn about God's universal and personal knowledge and power?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_11_4","questionText":"4. How does David's longing and request reveal his zeal for God and hatred of sin? How can a Christian balance hatred of sin and love for those opposed to God today? (Psalm 139:19-24)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Psalm","verse":"139:19-24"}]},{"id":"2018_11_5","questionText":"5. How is this Psalm relevant to your present circumstances? (Are you trying to run from Him, being honest with Him, feeling persecuted, etc.?)","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"three":{"title":"THIRD DAY: Read Psalms 7 and 10.\nPsalms 7 and 10 demonstrate praise and petition through suffering.","questions":[{"id":"2018_11_6","questionText":"6. Which attributes of God stand out to you? Why?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_11_7","questionText":"7. What do these psalms reveal about those who perpetrate wickedness and those who are afflicted?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_11_8","questionText":"8. Who and what is David's constant hope? Who and what is your hope?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"four":{"title":"FOURTH DAY: Read Psalm 19\nDavid praised God's revelation in creation and His Word.","readVerse":[{"book":"Psalm","verse":"19:1-999"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_11_9","questionText":"9. God's glory has been defined as the sum total of His attributes. What attributes of God are revealed through creation? (Use any Scripture reference.)","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_11_10","questionText":"10. How does David describe God's Word? How is your attitude toward God's Word similar or different?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_11_11","questionText":"11. How does David describe the benefits of studying God's Word? What specific differences has studying God's Word made in you?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"five":{"title":"FIFTH DAY: Read Psalms 2 and 110.\nDavid pleaded for deliverance often and in confident, prophetic anticipation of Jesus Christ.","questions":[{"id":"2018_11_12","questionText":"12. What is the complaint against God in Psalm 2:1-3? How does this compare with people's complaints against God today?","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Psalm","verse":"2:1-3"}]},{"id":"2018_11_13","questionText":"13. What is God's gracious answer to the world's rebellion? How can God justly spare all the wicked who take refuge in his Son? (See Psalm 2:4-13 and Isaiah 53:4-6.)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Psalm","verse":"2:4-13"},{"book":"Isaiah","verse":"53:4-6"}]},{"id":"2018_11_14","questionText":"14. What does Psalm 110 reveal about Jesus? (For help, see Acts 2:33-36; Mark 14:61-62; Hebrews 1:13; 4:14-16; 7:11-8:2 or any other scripture references.)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Psalm","verse":"110:1-999"},{"book":"Acts","verse":"2:33-36"},{"book":"Mark","verse":"14:61-62"},{"book":"Hebrews","verse":"1:13"},{"book":"Hebrews","verse":"4:14-16"},{"book":"Hebrews","verse":"7:11-8:2"}]},{"id":"2018_11_15","questionText":"15. What conviction, confidence or hope do these psalms give you today?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"six":{"title":"SIXTH DAY: Review Psalms 2, 7, 10, 19, 110, 139.","questions":[{"id":"2018_11_16","questionText":"16. Choose one or more verses from this week's lesson, and quietly think deeply (meditate) on what is written. How is God calling you to take to heart and act on these verses? Share with your group what God has revealed to you.","answer":"","quotes":[]}]}}}